Asking for calls up and divide, they will
also remain bullish and you ca
n't miss your decision soft toys,
money is made more quickly,
if there is a fall, there are two names on it, one
because of our foot, the second is JSW
Steel, after MP Olympic Jewellers,
we will have fun today by scrolling a little in the pimple,
type this point to 501 and deliver it in the final match,
so because of this we will put a shotgun 530 pack and will set a
target of 9052 targets of five,
leaving it on the side, we will put all India in it and the
second stop is JSW Steel
's better school result correction
and whatever has been going on for the last few days,
profit booking has started in Beed Metals, Pet Cement and Steel, Tata Motors Pune, so
like we can put a valley school in
Amritsar around 415 and in that
we will make a key and go that 4G
ok 4G net, then 404 will be a tiger for you,
for which W Steel, stoploss of 415,
meet in here, selling  The
opinion is of and the second name is Bajaj Finance where
you can see the levels around 5390 5350, the
right is visible at 5450 throughout the day
but the labels for you are
meeting around 5350,
you can maintain a stoploss of 5530 here
but the pressure now is the entry line for this, so what is this, due to
selling pressure in the market, let's
talk about some good stars in it,
coming here, the insurance press
creation has been the favorite, HDFC Life, SBI
Life, ICICI Prudential, IAS,
Ward, Subway, shopping and running
enterprises were seen coming in the last in Salumbar,
you would like to pick any name from
these four,
all your troubles are very good, from the hot insurance
sector level, a lot of good clean
water, if the market stabilizes, if it
stabilizes only after solid, then it
becomes a good bond to keep an eye on the boats,
so if we talk about it, you can get goosebumps
on duty and debit the receiver
mantras and  910 and in the same way if we
talk about ICICI General Insurance
then it has also closed at a very good level and high
wanted near A, then a
flow through can be formed in it, if it
gets support from more traders then this rally
can be held in a more beautiful manner and the entry of ICICI General Insurance will be at
1566 but if it gets Bigg
Boss market correction and Honey Singh will get
more growth and will put a mystery in front of England on the
top forex broker and
our target will be 1500 and 1540 ok so
1530 1540 this cut
for buying here if you
get below then it will be a better option
in isolation ward 21 by the way if you like this creation on beans then
you will see SBI Life on the screen
you can buy here for the strength of ₹100 note 910
ok
I want to talk to you about Titan but
before that Deepali was present she
also has a preview of Titan what kind of numbers can come, they are going to
rain pen so let's
talk to Deepali first then we will discuss with you
we will a  The Diwali forecast is tightening
in
that the title number six is ​​quoted. If
we look at the revenue profitability and beta front, then growth of 15 to 1718
portions is expected on all three fronts. Margin
was there but it is likely to remain flat. Earlier,
due to 149 percent, there is
compression as you can read the existing Escort Amazon points.
However, the
demand has been very strong in the festive season and wedding season. We have
got the benefit of united painter demand, hence whatever is recent, there is a
possibility of good performance. According to the
data shared in the company link, the
jewellery segment has shown
pain in 15.03. Apart from this, if you
look at this segment, it also saw a
very strong recovery compared to the previous quarter. On the
other hand, 90% recovery was seen in Ayurveda. Let's
talk about AgustaWestland. If there is a
recovery of around 15 to 20 percent in your third line pass, then
now there can be another oil depot where growth of around
15 to 20 percent is
expected.  You can assume a growth of 15 to 20 percent
and
in many sectors, there is
a good recovery on a sequential basis every minute. The
market is moving on the assumption of
Rachna. How did you see the charts of Titan?
Today it was in a good boom, there was a jump of 100 percent.
Even in a falling market, it kept
itself composed. What should be done
for this?
And the person whose nature and memory is
also authorized distributor, this top picture,
its chanting also gives results, after that it is
always good on this. Warden Quarter is
delivering good results.
If you cannot time the result
till the end, it is good today, then it is like always,
after the result it seems to be very desperate. So
if all this happens, we will make a long stop in it
and we will take such a person at 1538 and don't get it,
1580 quote 16, then 1580
1602 will be the target, you can maintain a stop loss of 1538.
Sometimes the
stock closes around 1560. It has been seen that good
album has talked about it.  Bharti Airtel had done this or
play it back that even today it was
managing itself in the falling market, it has
given a day in the future around 603 604 only,
in the falling market it was able to fold the additional of BHU,
now what are you seeing that like the same,
family help
creativity is seen increasing, what should be done
and the
question is long time debit, this
is a disgusting point to take out the shot, there is no problem in the
chart and similarly if the support remains on this, the
file path is currently at 16022
of 585, if in cases of late support, as long as this
double remains, then
we can do the levels on the previous line and on the upper side,
Degi Silk Chiffon Remedy G 616
600 1624 these are the targets which you should keep in
mind in Bharti Airtel, you can move well
and in tow there are three names Mahindra &
Mahindra where profit-taking is there, Tata
Motors is profiting and Bajaj Auto, there is
Taurus, some chat has started, the
chart of I have come  You will like it distorted
but the correction is that
I will give you the eye of knowledge, from here it will
look at us one, two, three times on the upper side, so we will
clove in it, so we will do it above the 9th pipe, right now it
is around Ireland, Nobel
Prize, when it goes up then we will do it, then we will
put it like this and it will be debited, otherwise the
part of the hostel, okay, so you can keep an eye on Eminem
when it comes to photos.